var questions=[
    {
        num : 1,
        question : "",
        answer : "Papua New Guinea",
        options : [
            "Egypt",
            "Tanzania",
            "Nigeria",
            "Papua New Guinea",
        ]
    },
    {
    num : 2,
    question : "",
    answer : "Hawaii(US)",
    options : [
        "Uganda",
        "Fiji",
        "Hawaii(US)",
        "Algeria",
    ]
},
{
    num : 3,
    question : "",
    answer : "Solomon Islands",
    options : [
        "Solomon Islands",
        "Angola",
        "Guam(US)",
        "Kiribati",
    ]
},
{
    num : 4,
    question : "",
    answer : "Vanuatu",
    options : [
        "Mozambique",
        "Vanuatu",
        "Ivory Coast",
        "Niger",
    ]
},
{
    num : 5,
    question : "",
    answer : "Samoa",
    options : [
        "New Caledonia(France)",
        "Zambia",
        "Burkina Faso",
        "Samoa",
    ]
},
{
    num : 6,
    question : "",
    answer : "Kiribati",
    options : [
        "Kiribati",
        "Guam(US)",
        "Chad",
        "Benin",
    ]
},
{
    num : 7,
    question : "",
    answer : "Federated States of Micronesia",
    options : [
        "Namibia",
        "Eritrea",
        "Central African Republic",
        "Federated States of Micronesia",
    ]
},
{
    num : 8,
    question : "",
    answer : "American Samoa(US)",
    options : [
        "American Samoa(US)",
        "Northern Mariana Islands(US)",
        "Tonga",
        "Gabon",
    ]
},
{
    num : 9,
    question : "",
    answer : "Palau",
    options : [
        "Cape Verde",
        "Marshall Islands",
        "Palau",
        "Seychelles",
    ]
},
{
    num : 10,
    question : "",
    answer : "Nauru",
    options : [
        "Nauru",
        "Tuvalu",
        "Mauritius",
        "Djibouti",
    ]
},
{
    num : 11,
    question : "",
    answer : "Norfolk Island(Australia)",
    options : [
        "Sierra Leone",
        "Liberia",
        "Marshall Islands",
        "Norfolk Island(Australia)",
    ]
},
{
    num : 12,
    question : "",
    answer : "Niue(NZ)",
    options : [
        "Libya",
        "Eritrea",
        "Mauritania",
        "Niue(NZ)",
    ]
},
{
    num : 13,
    question : "",
    answer : "Tokelau(NZ)",
    options : [
        "Botswana",
        "Tokelau(NZ)",
        "Gabon",
        "Lesotho",
    ]
},
{
    num : 14,
    question : "",
    answer : "Pitcairn Islands(UK)",
    options : [
        "Ghana",
        "Tokelau (NZ)",
        "Pitcairn Islands(UK)",
        "Ethiopia",
    ]
},
{
    num : 15,
    question : "",
    answer : "Northern Mariana Islands",
    options : [
        "Northern Mariana Islands",
        "Congo",
        "Burkina Faso",
        "Republic of the Congo",
    ]
},
{
    num : 16,
    question : "",
    answer : "Guam(US)",
    options : [
        "Nigeria",
        "Samoa",
        "French Polynesia(France)",
        "Guam(US)",
    ]
},
{
    num : 17,
    question : "",
    answer : "Fiji",
    options : [
        "Ethiopia",
        "Fiji",
        "Ivory Coast",
        "Burkina Faso",
    ]
},
{
    num : 18,
    question : "",
    answer : "Cook Islands(NZ)",
    options : [
        "Senegal",
        "Senegal",
        "Palau",
        "Cook Islands(NZ)",
    ]
}
];